http://aristotlealert.com/privacy

866-748-5227
info@provecompliance.com
HomeResourcesBlogContact
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy was last updated on March 19, 2018Our Policy:Welcome to the web site (the “Site”) of Sergeant Laboratories, Inc. (“Sergeant Laboratories”, “AristotleInsight”, “AristotleInsight::K12”, “we”, “us” and/or “our”). This Site is operated by Sergeant Laboratories and has been created to provide information about our company and our services (together with the Site, the “Services”) to our Service visitors (“you”, “your”). This Privacy Policy sets forth Sergeant Laboratories’ policy with respect to information including personally identifiable data (“Personal Data”) and other information that is collected from visitors to the Site and Services.Information We Collect:When you interact with us through the Services, we may collect Personal Data and other information from you, as further described below:Personal Data That You Provide Through the Services: We collect Personal Data from you when you voluntarily provide such information, such as when you contact us with inquiries, request email subscription, register for access to the Services or use certain Services. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to: name, address, e-mail, address, company/organization, and telephone number. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by providing Personal Information to us, you allow others, including us, to identify you and therefore you may not be anonymous. Wherever Sergeant Laboratories collects Personal Data we make an effort to provide a link to this Privacy Policy.By voluntarily providing us with Personal Data, you are consenting to our use of it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data to the Services, you acknowledge and agree that such Personal Data may be transferred from your current location to the offices and servers of Sergeant Laboratories and the authorized third parties referred to herein located in the United States and Ireland.Other Information:Non-Identifiable Data: When you interact with Sergeant Laboratories through the Services, we receive and store certain personally non-identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Sergeant Laboratories may store such information itself or such information may be included in databases (which may be hosted by a third party service provider) owned and maintained by Sergeant Laboratories’ affiliates, agents or service providers. The Services may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, web requests, the data sent in response to such requests, the Internet Protocol (IP) address, the browser type, the browser language, a timestamp for the request, and the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers. It is important to note that no Personal Data is available or used in this process.In operating the Services, we may use a technology called “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Services gives to your browser when you access the Services. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Services and help us analyze Services usage more accurately. For instance, our Site may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Services without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the Site. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect Personal Data except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Service features.Aggregated Personal Data: In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, Sergeant Laboratories often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests and behavior based on the Personal Data and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and Sergeant Laboratories may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Sergeant Laboratories may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.Third Party Analytics: We may allow third party service providers to use cookies or similar technologies to collect information, which may include Personal Data, about you or your browsing activities on our Site or over time and across different websites following your use of the Services. For example, we use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site and enhance your experience when you use the Service. For more information on how Google uses this data, go to www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/. We also use StatCounter, a web analytics service provided by StatCounter. StatCounter also uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site and enhance your experience when you use the Service. For more information on how StatCounter uses this data, go to www.StatCounter.com/about/legal/#privacy/.Our Use of Your Personal Data and Other Information:Sergeant Laboratories uses the Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. If you provide Personal Data for a certain reason, we may use the Personal Data in connection with the reason for which it was provided. For instance, if you contact us by email, we will use the Personal Data you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. Also, if you provide Personal Data in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your Personal Data to provide you with access to such services and to monitor your use of such services. Sergeant Laboratories and its subsidiaries and affiliates (the “Related Companies”) may also use your Personal Data and other personally non-identifiable information collected through the Services to help us improve the content and functionality of the Services, to better understand our users and to improve the Services. While we collect and store IP address information, that information is not made public.If Sergeant Laboratories intends on using any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the Personal Data is collected.Sergeant Laboratories is operated from the United States. If you are visiting the Website from outside the U.S., you agree to any processing of any personal information you provide us according to this policy.Sergeant Laboratories may contact you, by email or other means. For example, Sergeant Laboratories may send you promotional emails relating to Sergeant Laboratories or other third parties we feel you would be interested in, or communicate with you about your use of the Sergeant Laboratories website. Sergeant Laboratories may also use technology to alert us via a confirmation email when you open an email from us. You can modify your email notification preferences by clicking the appropriate link included in the footer of email notifications. If you do not want to receive email from Sergeant Laboratories, please opt out of receiving emails at the bottom of any Sergeant Laboratories emails or by contacting us via the information provided below.We also use social buttons provided by services like Twitter, Google+, LinkedIn and Facebook. Your use of these third party services is entirely optional. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these third party services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those third party services’ privacy policies.Our Disclosure of Your Personal Data and Other Information:Sergeant Laboratories is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your Personal Data with certain third parties without further notice to you, as set forth below:Business Transfers: As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets.Related Companies: We may also share your Personal Data with our Related Companies for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy.Agents, Consultants and Related Third Parties: Sergeant Laboratories, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents, Consultants, and Related Third Parties.Legal Requirements: Sergeant Laboratories may disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of Sergeant Laboratories, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and spam/malware prevention.Your Choices:You can visit the Site without providing any Personal Data. If you choose not to provide any Personal Data, you may not be able to use certain Services.Exclusions:This Privacy Policy does not apply to any Personal Data collected by Sergeant Laboratories other than Personal Data collected through the Services. This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to Sergeant Laboratories through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and Sergeant Laboratories shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.Children:Sergeant Laboratories does not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not submit any Personal Data through the Services. We encourage parents and legal guardians to monitor their children’s Internet usage and to help enforce our Privacy Policy by instructing their children never to provide Personal Data on the Services without their permission. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personal Data to Sergeant Laboratories through the Services, please contact us, and we will endeavor to delete that information from our databases.Links to Other Web Sites:This Privacy Policy applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by Sergeant Laboratories (the “Third Party Sites”). The policies and procedures we described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that Sergeant Laboratories endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.Security:Sergeant Laboratories takes appropriate measures to protect the Personal Data provided via the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any Personal Data to Sergeant Laboratories via the Internet.Other Terms and Conditions:Your access to and use of the Services is subject to the Terms of Service at www.sgtlabs.com/terms-and-conditions.Changes to Sergeant Laboratories’ Privacy Policy:The Services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for Sergeant Laboratories to make changes to this Privacy Policy. Sergeant Laboratories reserves the right to update or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice. Please review this policy periodically, and especially before you provide any Personal Data. This Privacy Policy was last updated on the date indicated above. If we make major changes in the way we collect or use information, we will attempt to notify you by posting an announcement on the Website or sending you an email. Your continued use of the Services after any changes or revisions to this Privacy Policy shall indicate your agreement with the terms of such revised Privacy Policy.Access to Information; Contacting Sergeant Laboratories:To keep your Personal Data accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct Personal Data in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Services.Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about Sergeant Laboratories’ Privacy Policy or the information practices of the Services.You may contact us as follows: info@provecompliance.com
Home
AristotleInsight
AristotleK12
Contact
Blog
Resources
Terms
Privacy
CONTACT US:
866-748-5227
info@provecompliance.com
FOLLOW US:
Copyright All Rights Reserved © 2000 - 2020
